







Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Current Designation: Technical Product Owner

Current Company: Honeywell Technology Solutions Lab Pvt

Ltd

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Technical Product Owner, Full Stack Developer, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Programming, Cloud Computing, Software Design, Agile Methodology, Predictive Modeling, Software Architecture, Machine

Total Experience: 13 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

intelligence and Machine Learning]

Highest Degree: MS/MSc(Science) [Artificial

Notice Period: 2 Months

Learning,SQL,C++,C#,Azure,MongoDB

Verified : Email - id

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021 Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Jump to Section

A Software development professional and a Technical product Owner comes with 12 years of experience develop/handling Enterprise multi-tier applications, Desktop Applications, Cross Platform Mobile App development, Cloud and a Data Science Enthusiast.

Work Experience

- Honeywell Technology Solutions Lab Pvt Ltd as Technical Product Owner Jun 2013 to Till Date
- Honeywell Technology Solutions Lab Pvt Ltd as Technical Product Owner Jun 2013 to Jun 2013
- Siemens International as Senior Software Engineer Jan 2011 to Jun 2013
- WIPRO Technologies as Software Engineer / Senior Software Engineer Jan 2008 to Jan 2011

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from Anna University in 2007

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Artificial intelligence and Machine Learning) from Liverpool John Morees University in 2020

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: PG Program in Machine Learning & Artificial Intelligence

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name

Version Last Used Experience

Fyllioli, Off, Java Suipi, Reau, Muie
.Net Programming (.Net Core, C#, WPF)
Structured (SQL) and No-SQL (Mongo DB)
Linear/Logistic Regression, SVM
Random Forests, Gradient Boosted trees
Deep learning

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.